https://swedishhill.com/shop-online/shopping-policies/

Producers of Riesling, Vidal Blanc, Cabernet Franc, Cayuga White, and great Sparkling and Dessert Wines.
New York's only 3 time winner of the Governor's Cup.
Home of Doobie the Donkey.
Sign-Up for our Newsletter
Order History
My Shopping Cart
Shop Online
MenuHomeExperience SwedishHistory – The Story Behind the WineTasting RoomGroup ReservationsWinemaker’s CellarDoobie & SvenShop OnlineHoliday ShopSpecialsWhitesRedsRosésSparklingsDessert & SpiritsJuiceBasketsWine ClubPersonalized LabelsFavor BottlesGift ShopGift CardsOnline Shopping PoliciesOrder HistoryOur LocationsSwedish Hill WinerySwedish Hill Lake PlacidGoose Watch WineryGoose Watch Lake PlacidPenguin Bay WineryRetail Stores and RestaurantsAwards/MedalsWhitesRedsSparklingsDessertsInfo/AccessibilityAccessibility PolicyHours and DirectionsContact UsEvents2020 Events CalendarOff Premise EventsEvent Pairings and Recipes
Sign-Up for our Newsletter
Order History
My Shopping Cart
Online Shopping Policies
Privacy Policy
When you do business with Swedish Hill Winery you can expect that your personal information will be kept private and confidential. At Swedish Hill Winery we are committed to maintaining your privacy and safeguarding your account, transaction, and personal information. Such information is considered confidential and non-public.
Obtaining Information
Swedish Hill Winery collects certain confidential information from you as a customer. Examples of the type of information collected include addresses, phone numbers, and product preferences. You supply some of this information to Swedish Hill Winery on order forms and other forms.
Credit Card Information
Swedish Hill Winery does not collect your credit card numbers or ever see them. When you are asked for credit card information you will be on the Foxycart website, a payment processing company of excellent reputation that is fully in compliance with privacy and banking regulations.
Contact Information
Several of our optional services may involve storing personal information – your Personal Shopping Account, Tell Me when services, Newsletter subscriptions and so forth. This is for your convenience only. The information is not used for any other purpose.
Internet Opt Out Notification
Swedish Hill Winery may disclose non-exempted, non-public personal information, including transaction and experience information, to its affiliates for solicitation or marketing additional products and services. You may elect to opt out of such disclosure by clicking here and selecting your preferences.
Postal and Phone Opt Out Notification
If you place orders by mail or phone, we do not make our mailing list available to any company or person.
Return Policy
With receipt: Swedish Hill Vineyard, Inc. will gladly return any defective wine or merchandise purchased within the last 30 days.  You must bring the product back with receipt in order to receive a full refund.  You will be credited back via your method of payment (cash, credit, or gift card).  You must have the credit card used at the time of purchase for credit card returns.
Without a receipt: Swedish Hill Vineyard, Inc. will gladly return any defective wine or merchandise.  If no receipt is present, you will be required to show your license.  Refund amount will be given at the lowest sale price offered in the last 30 days and will be issued in the form of a gift certificate or store credit. There is a restocking fee for all online returns.
Shipping Policies
Recipient Restrictions & Signing for Shipments
By placing an order for an alcoholic beverage through our website, you formally represent that you are at least 21 years of age and that the intended recipient of the shipment is at least 21 years of age. The recipient will be required to show identification that that proves he or she is at least 21 years old and will be required to sign for the delivery. If the recipient cannot provide identification proving their age or the recipient’s home is vacant, the delivery will be re- attempted three times until the recipient is present and can provide identification. After the third attempt, if no one has been present to sign for the alcohol shipment, the shipment will then be returned to our facilities at the purchasers cost. There is  25% restocking fee for all online returns.
Shipping
We will ship Mondays, Wednesdays & Fridays (weather depending) using FedEx. Please allow up 3-5 business days for your order to be charged and processed, plus the estimated shipping time frame pending on your location. If you have any questions about your order or its delivery status, please contact us either calling us toll free (888-549-WINE) or email us at info@SwedishHill.com. For rush deliveries please call us at 888-549-WINE.
Shipping Destinations
State laws restrict or prevent shipping wine directly to consumers in some states. Deliveries can only be made to physical addresses. We cannot ship to Post Office boxes or APO/FPO addresses. Some states restrict the amount a consumer can have shipped from a winery.
[top]
Site Design and Hosting: In House Graphic Design Inc.
© Swedish Hill Winery All Rights Reserved
